### #1 Google Integrator
    
    We have the best website integration tools for Google and Office 365.

    ### Trusted Data & Hosting
    
    SchoolBlocks uses the most modern and scalable tech-stack hosted on AWS.

    ### Best UI Design
    
    Fun & easy drag-n-drop makes page management a breeze.

    ### The ultimate school communication app.
    
    An app for each school with Google Classroom, Schoology and Canvas integrations! ParentSquare, ClassTag, Zippslip and more!

    ### ADA, WCAG 2.0 & CIPA Compliance
    
    We work closely with government officials and children with special needs to ensure everyone is successful.

Privacy Policy
--------------

### Information Collection and Use

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, this information is protected both online and offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information.

### Use of Personal Information

We do not collect any personal information unless you voluntarily provide it by sending us email, participating in a survey, or completing an online form. Personal information submitted will not be transferred to any non-affiliated third parties unless otherwise stated at the time of collection. When a user submits personally identifiable information it is used only for the purpose stated at the time of collection.

Users who login via Google, Office365, Facebook, or any other identity provider, automatically share their first name, last name, and email address with our system. Our system saves this information and displays it to the user and, if specified by the school district, in a profile card that is publicly available in an official staff directory. No other personal information from Google, Office365, or Facebook is saved in our system.

**Right to delete**  
Upon verifiable request we will delete personal information we have collected about you and will inform our client (i.e. the school or district) of the request.

### Consent

Where consent for the use and disclosure of personal information is required, the school will seek consent from the appropriate person. In the case of a student’s personal information, the school will seek the consent from the student and/ or parent depending on the circumstances and the student’s mental ability and maturity to understand the consequences of the proposed use and disclosure.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file stored by your browser that allows the website to “remember” your preferences such as calendar settings and site bookmarks on the site from visit to visit, or to maintain your “logged in” status when visiting protected areas. Use of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Web browsers have settings allowing you to reject cookies, or selectively accept cookies, or delete cookies previously accepted. Please be aware that rejecting or deleting cookies from our website may make certain functions unavailable to you.

SchoolBlocks is a school district website solution offering Google Apps for Education, Office 365 and other leading apps.

[417 Main Street Suite U

Carbondale, CO 81623](https://www.google.com/maps/place/417+Main+St,+Carbondale,+CO+81623,+USA/@39.4007575,-107.2138825,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x8741ab930d955bbb:0x4364e7c3bfc39408!8m2!3d39.4007534!4d-107.2116938?hl=en-US&shorturl=1)

Copyright @2022 School Blocks

> "Really nice, user-friendly, easy to teach anybody. I'm sold on this!"

—Sean Johnson, **Lawton County Schools**

Schedule a demo of SchoolBlocks
-------------------------------
